Guide to the Beer Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- FAMILY: GENERAL, 1851-1969; Series I; 22.7' (55 boxes)
  - Financial Files
    - Family Real Estate and Property
      - Yonkers Property: correspondence with attorneys, 1938-1947 (Box 31, Folder 362-363)
      - Yonkers Property: correspondence and notes re: alteration and sale (1), 1937-1939 (Box 31, Folder 364)
      - Yonkers Property: correspondence and notes re: alteration and sale (2), 1937-1944 (Box 31, Folder 365)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - correspondence, bills and receipts, 1935-1945 (Box 31, Folder 366-368)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - correspondence, bills and receipts, 1946-1947, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 369)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - correspondence, receipts, lists, 1955-1957, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 370)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - correspondence, bills and receipts in regard to sale of and insurance for painting by Thomas Hart Benton, 1940-1943, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 371)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - notes, lists and catalogues (1), 1938-1945 (Box 32, Folder 372)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - notes, lists and catalogues (2), 1938-1945 (Box 32, Folder 373)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - notes, lists and catalogues (3), 1938-1945 (Box 32, Folder 374)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - lists of books by subject or type, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 375)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - lists of books stored in house, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 376)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - lists of books sent to Swann Auction Galleries, catalogue, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 377)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - lists of books not found in Swann catalogue, 1945 November (Box 33, Folder 378)
      - Yonkers Property: disposition of books and furnishings - lists of books by subject, type or author, notes and receipts, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 379)
      - Yonkers Property: floor plans and Siasconset Property: maps of property lots, Circa 1880-1890, undated (Box 33, Folder 380)
    - Linus Caleb Baldwin
      - Accounts and minutes of meetings of the Bellevernon Branch of the Pittsburgh and Connellsville Railroad.
        See: box 47, folder 514
      - affidavits and legal notices, 1885-1900 (Box 34, Folder 381)
      - bills and receipts, 1854-1882 (Box 34, Folder 382-390)
      - bills and receipts, 1883-1908, undated (Box 35, Folder 391-395)
      - canceled checks, 1872-1900 (Box 35, Folder 396-397)
      - cash accounts book, 1867-1873 (Box 35, Folder 398)
      - certificate of land grant to Joseph A. McGonigle for land in Wyoming Territory, signed by Chester A. Arthur, 1885 (Box 35, Folder 399)
        See: box 180
      - contracts, deeds and mortgages, 1856-1908 (Box 35, Folder 400-403)
      - insurance and stocks, 1889, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 404)
      - ledger of income and expenses for various ranches and farms in which L.C.B. held an interest or owned, 1883-1888 (Box 36, Folder 405)
      - memoranda book, primarily an inventory of L.C.B.'s estate, 1868-1873 (Box 36, Folder 406)
      - memoranda books (4), 1873-1891, undated (Box 36, Folder 407)
    - Alice Baldwin Beer
      - bank books, 1910-1939 (Box 36, Folder 408)
      - bills and receipts, 1907-1968 (Box 36, Folder 409)
      - canceled checks, bank statements, 1931-1939 (Box 36, Folder 410)
      - income tax records, 1950-1954 (Box 36, Folder 411)
      - insurance, 1915, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 412)
      - ration books (Box 36, Folder 413)
      - will, 1931 (Box 36, Folder 414)
    - Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer
      - bank pass books, canceled checks, insurance, 1911-1912, 1916 (Box 36, Folder 415)
      - bank statement, canceled checks, 1928 (Box 36, Folder 416)
      - bank statements, 1933-1934, 1939-1944 (Box 36, Folder 417-420)
      - bills and receipts (1), 1917-1937 (Box 37, Folder 421)
      - bills and receipts (2), 1917-1937 (Box 37, Folder 422)
      - bills and receipts (3), 1917-1937 (Box 37, Folder 423)
      - bills and receipts (4), 1917-1937 (Box 37, Folder 424)
      - bills and receipts (1), 1938-1943 (Box 37, Folder 425)
      - bills and receipts (2), 1938-1943 (Box 37, Folder 426)
      - canceled checks, 1933-1934, 1938-1939 (Box 37, Folder 427-428)
      - canceled checks, receipts, checkbook, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 429)
      - checkbooks, 1935-1939 (Box 38, Folder 430-431)
      - estate of M.A.A.B.B. correspondence, 1938, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 432)
      - estate of M.A.A.B.B: lists of personal belongings, 1940 (Box 38, Folder 433)
      - estate of M.A.A.B.B notes by Alice Baldwin Beer, 1939-1940 (Box 38, Folder 434)
      - stocks, 1903-1939 (Box 38, Folder 435)
    - Richard Cameron Beer
      - consular service salary and settlement of accounts, 1919-1928 (Box 39, Folder 436)
      - personal financial information, 1918-1934 (Box 39, Folder 437)
    - Judge Thomas Beer
      - financial papers, 1869-1907 (Box 39, Folder 438)
    - Thomas Beer
      - apartment rental, 1938-1939 (Box 39, Folder 439)
      - bank book, 1909 (Box 39, Folder 440)
      - bills and receipts, 1908-1940 (Box 39, Folder 441-443)
      - medical bills, 1937-1940 (Box 39, Folder 444)
      - box office receipts for The Plot Thickens, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 445)
      - canceled checks, 1909-1912, 1922-1924 (Box 39, Folder 446-447)
      - canceled checks, 1925-1930 (Box 40, Folder 448-453)
      - canceled checks, 1931-1934 (Box 41, Folder 454-457)
      - canceled checks, 1935-1938 (Box 42, Folder 458-459)
      - contract for In Freedom's Name, 1922 (Box 42, Folder 460)
      - contracts with Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1930-1939 (Box 42, Folder 461)
      - estate settlement, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 462)
      - funeral expenses, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 463)
      - income taxes, 1928-1934 (Box 42, Folder 464)
      - insurance, 1905-1940 (Box 42, Folder 465)
      - memoranda book, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 466)
      - property in Palo Alto: bills, floor plan for a house, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 467)
      - royalty statements, 1923-1940, 1944-1970 (Box 42, Folder 468-469)
    - William Collins Beer
      - bills and receipts, 1892-1912 May (Box 43, Folder 470-480)
      - bills and receipts, 1912 June-Dec, 1913 January-1914 January (Box 44, Folder 481-491)
      - bills and receipts, 1914 February-1917, undated (Box 45, Folder 492-500)
      - canceled checks, 1900-1903, 1908, 1910-1911 (Box 45, Folder 501-503)
      - canceled checks, 1912-1913 (Box 46, Folder 504-505)
      - estate: bills and receipts, 1916-1917 (Box 46, Folder 506)
      - estate: correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 46, Folder 507)
      - estate: inventory of his private library, 1916-1938 (Box 46, Folder 508)
      - estate: settlement of accounts, by Martha A. A. Beer as administratrix, 1916-1919 (Box 46, Folder 509)
      - estate: bank statements, canceled checks, bank pass book, checkbooks, 1916-1919 (Box 46, Folder 510)
      - insurance, 1895-1916 (Box 46, Folder 511)
    - Mary Elizabeth (Beer) Lothian
      - financial papers, 1905-1909 (Box 46, Folder 512)
  - Personal Files
    - Alice (Boyle) Baldwin
      - autograph album, 1859-1862 (Box 47, Folder 513)
      - diary and household accounts, 1874, 1882-1884 (Box 47, Folder 514)
      - manuscripts, undated (Box 47, Folder 515)
      - Mountain Female Seminary (Pennsylvania), 1862 (Box 47, Folder 516)
    - Robert Caleb Baldwin
      - memorabilia, 1893-1901 (Box 47, Folder 517)
    - Margaret Cameron Beer
      - memorabilia, 1907-1911 (Box 47, Folder 518)
    - Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer
      - addresses and calling cards, undated (Box 47, Folder 519)
      - autograph album, 1879 (Box 47, Folder 520)
      - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1919-1939 (Box 47, Folder 521)
      - recipes, undated (Box 47, Folder 522)
      - travel diary, 1890 (Box 47, Folder 523)
      - travel diaries, notes, 1909, 1928 (Box 47, Folder 524)
      - Up-to-Date Club, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 525)
      - Vassar College notebooks, undated (Box 48, Folder 526-527)
      - Vassar College scrapbook, Circa 1880 (Box 48, Folder 528)
      - Vassar College sketchbook, undated (Box 49, Folder 529)
      - Yonkers Homeopathic Hospital and Maternity: newspaper clippings and printed matter, 1907-1929 (Box 49, Folder 530)
      - memorabilia, undated (Box 49, Folder 531)
    - Tabitha Mary (Dinsmore) Beer
      - manuscripts, 1827, n.d (Box 49, Folder 532)
    - Reverend Thomas Beer
      - notebooks., 1827, n.d (Box 49, Folder 533)
        See also: boxes 26-27, folders 317-326
      - Vermillion Institute (Ohio), 1851-1856, 1873 (Box 49, Folder 534)
    - Judge Thomas Beer
      - advertisement booklet for his cattle, 1878 (Box 49, Folder 535)
      - commission as judge in the Circuit Court of Ohio, 1891 (Box 49, Folder 536)
      - diary, 1891 (Box 49, Folder 537)
      - Familiar Faces of Ohio (Box 49, Folder 538)
      - legal briefs, undated (Box 49, Folder 539)
      - legal opinions, 1880, undated (Box 49, Folder 540)
      - political printed matter, 1896 (Box 50, Folder 541)
      - scrapbook. (Box 50, Folder 541)
        See Folio box 173
      - speeches(printed) and other manuscripts, 1867, 1909, undated (Box 50, Folder 542)
      - memorabilia (Box 50, Folder 543)
    - Mary Elizabeth (Beer) Lothian
      - diary, 1907 May-June (Box 50, Folder 544)
      - manuscripts, 1898, undated (Box 50, Folder 545)
      - programs and reviews; marriage notices, Circa 1910 (Box 50, Folder 546)
      - textbooks and catalog for University of Wooster, undated (Box 50, Folder 547)
      - memorabilia, undated (Box 50, Folder 548)
    - Dorcas Katherine (Beer) Reece
      - memorabilia, undated (Box 50, Folder 549)
    - Helen McCormick (Baldwin) Tyler
      - school notebook, undated (Box 50, Folder 550)
    - General
      - manuscripts, n d. (Box 50, Folder 551)
      - recipes, undated (Box 51, Folder 552)
      - school programs, 1854-1933 (Box 51, Folder 553)
      - theater programs, 1877-1987 (Box 51, Folder 554)
      - valentines, gift cards, 1893, undated (Box 51, Folder 555)
      - memorabilia, 1853, undated (Box 51, Folder 556)
  - Photographs
    - Baldwin, Alice (Boyle), undated (Box 51, Folder 557)
    - Baldwin, Linus Caleb, undated (Box 51, Folder 558)
    - Baldwin, Robert Caleb, Circa 1898-1899 (Box 51, Folder 559)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin., Circa 1890-1941 (Box 51, Folder 560)
      See also: box 178
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin; album, Circa 1900-1912 (Box 51, Folder 561)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin; trip to Europe and Egypt., 1911 (Box 51, Folder 562)
      See also; box 176
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin: trip to Europe and Egypt (negatives), 1911 (Box 52, Folder 563-564)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin; miscellaneous negatives, 1911-1912 (Box 52, Folder 565)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin: trip to Spain (negatives and photographs), 1928-1929, 1936 (Box 52, Folder 566-567)
    - Beer, Dorcas Grizzel, undated (Box 52, Folder 568)
    - Beer, Katherine Jeanette, undated (Box 52, Folder 568)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin), circa 1865-1886, circa 1890-1939 (Box 52, Folder 569-570)
    - Beer, Richard Cameron (including Elizabeth (Thompson) Beer and Doris (Riker) Beer), Circa 1900-1930 (Box 52, Folder 571)
    - Beer, Richard Cameron (including Doris (Riker) Beer), Circa 1940-1957, undated (Box 53, Folder 572)
    - Beer, Richard Cameron: Mackenzie School photographs.
      See: box 53, folder 577
    - Beer, Tabitha Mary (Dinsmore), undated (Box 53, Folder 573)
    - Beer, Rev. Thomas, Circa 1834 (Box 53, Folder 574)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas, undated (Box 53, Folder 574)
    - Beer, Thomas., Circa 1890-1920 (Box 53, Folder 575)
    - Beer, Thomas, Circa 1922.1940 (Box 53, Folder 576)
    - Beer, Thomas: album, Circa 1907-1911 (Box 53, Folder 577)
    - Beer, Thomas: Mackenzie School and Yale College photographs., Circa 1880-1910
      See: box 53, folder 572
    - Beer, William Collins, Circa 1880-1910 (Box 54, Folder 578)
    - Dinsmore, William A. Hill, Mabel (Dinsmore), undated (Box 54, Folder 579)
    - Lothian, Mary Elizabeth (Beer) Reece, Dorcas Katherine (Beer)Tyler, Helen M. (Baldwin), 1920, undated (Box 54, Folder 580)
    - Tyler, James W., undated (Box 54, Folder 581)
    - Tyler, John Baldwin and Jane, Circa 1938-1941 (Box 54, Folder 582)
    - family groups (1), Circa 1860-1935 (Box 54, Folder 583)
    - family groups (2), Circa 1865-1935 (Box 54, Folder 584)
    - family and friends at Siasconset, Nantucket (negatives), [1907?] (Box 54, Folder 585)
    - friends of family members, Circa 1890-1935 (Box 54, Folder 586)
    - family homes and other locations, Circa 1890-1935 (Box 54, Folder 587)
    - unidentified, undated (Box 54, Folder 588)
  - Genealogy and Biography
    - Aten family genealogy (Box 54, Folder 589)
    - Baldwin family genealogy (Box 54, Folder 590)
    - Beer, Thomas (d. 1809): military, records (Box 54, Folder 591)
    - Beer family biographies (Box 55, Folder 592)
    - Beer family genealogy (Box 55, Folder 593)
    - Beer family obituaries, 1910-1944, undated (Box 55, Folder 594)
    - Beer family and Bucyrus, Ohio: clippings, 1905-1944 (Box 55, Folder 595)
    - Boyle family genealogy (Box 55, Folder 596)
    - Dinsmore family genealogy (Box 55, Folder 597)
    - Dinsmore family obituaries, 1920-1942, undated (Box 55, Folder 598)
    - Neel family genealogy (Box 55, Folder 599)
    - Pitney, Benjamin and Pitney family genealogy (Box 55, Folder 600)
- WILLIAM COLLINS BEER, 1880-1917; Series II; 15.6' (38 boxes)
  Correspondence is arranged chronologically and is preceded by an index of important correspondents. Letters for a particular day are arranged alphabetically by writer; letters written by William Collins Beer are filed at the end of the day's correspondence. Correspondence of others is filed in the general chronological sequence under the name of the addressee. Letters of condolence, letterpress books (which contain much of Beer's outgoing correspondence) and a special section of New York Life Insurance Company correspondence are filed at the end of the section.
  Information Files is arranged alphabetically by topic.
  Personal Files is arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Correspondence
    - 1881-1896 September (Box 56, Folder 1-15)
    - 1896 October-1901 Jan, undated (Box 57, Folder 16-28)
    - 1901 February-1902 July (Box 58, Folder 29-38)
    - 1902 August-1903 May 1-15 (Box 59, Folder 39-50)
    - 1903 May-1905 February (Box 60, Folder 51-65)
    - 1905 March-1906 June (Box 61, Folder 66-78)
    - 1906 July-1907 November (Box 62, Folder 79-91)
    - 1907 December-1909 February (Box 63, Folder 92-105)
    - 1909 March-1910 March 31 (Box 64, Folder 106-118)
    - 1910 April-1910 October 31 (Box 65, Folder 119-131)
    - 1910 November-1911 April 15-25 (Box 66, Folder 132-144)
    - 1911 April 26-1911 October 31 (Box 67, Folder 145-157)
    - 1911 November-1912 February 29. (Box 68, Folder 158-171)
    - 1912 March 1-1912 July 31 (Box 69, Folder 172-185)
    - 1912 August 1 - December 17 (Box 70, Folder 186-199)
    - 1912 December 18-1913 February 21 (Box 71, Folder 200-212)
    - 1913 February 22-1913 May 31 (Box 72, Folder 213-225)
    - 1913 June 1-1913 October 21 (Box 73, Folder 226-238)
    - 1913 October 22-1914 March 16 (Box 74, Folder 239-252)
    - 1914 March 17-1914 September 30 (Box 75, Folder 253-268)
    - 1914 October 1-1915 May 24 (Box 76, Folder 269-281)
    - 1915 May 25-1915 September 30 (Box 77, Folder 282-294)
    - 1915 October 1-1916 February 29 (Box 78, Folder 295-310)
    - 1916 March 1-1916 August 31 (Box 79, Folder 311-326)
    - 1916 September 1-1916 November (Box 80, Folder 327-331)
    - 1916 undated (Box 80, Folder 332)
    - 1917 (Box 80, Folder 333)
    - letters of condolence on death of William Collins Beer, A-H, 1916 (Box 80, Folder 334)
    - letters of condolence on death of William Collins Beer, J-Z, 1916 (Box 80, Folder 335)
    - undated letters addressed to WCB (Box 80, Folder 336-338)
    - undated and unidentified (Box 80, Folder 339)
    - letterpress book, 1890-1898, 1891-1895, 1909-1910 (Box 81, Folder 340-342)
    - letterpress book, 1893-1898 (Box 82, Folder 343-346)
    - letterpress book, 1897-1898, 1903-1905, 1907, 1911, 1913-1914 (Box 83, Folder 347-348)
    - New York Life Insurance Company investigation., 1906-1907 (Box 84, Folder 349)
      See also: box 84, folder 350
    - The People of the State of New York v. George W. Perkins., 1907 (Box 84, Folder 350)
      See also: boxes 86-90, folders 359-426
    - New York Life Insurance Company: Treasury Department letterpress book, 1902 January May (Box 84, Folder 351)
    - New York Life Insurance Company- J. P. Morgan & Co. correspondence: Navigation Bond Syndicate, 1902 April-1906 April (Box 84, Folder 352-353)
    - New York Life Insurance Company-J. S. Morgan & Co. (London) correspondence: United Collieries 5% Debenture Syndicate, 1902 July-1906 October (Box 84, Folder 354-355)
    - New York Life Insurance Company-New York Security & Trust Company correspondence; U. S. Steel Corporation Syndicate and railroad stocks, 1902 January-May, 1902 July-1904 May (Box 84, Folder 356-358)
    - oversize correspondence (Box 85, Folder 356-358)
  - Information files
    - Agreements entered into by WCB, 1889-1915 (Box 86, Folder 359)
    - Agreements not involving WCB, 1895-1915 (Box 86, Folder 360)
    - American Rapid Boat Company, undated (Box 86, Folder 361)
    - Ammunition, 1915-1916, undated (Box 86, Folder 362)
    - Beer (William C.) v. United Surety Company, 1910-1911 (Box 86, Folder 363)
    - Biographical information on: Lewis Stuyvesant Chandler, P. V. DeGraw, John J. McCook, George W. Perkins, E. A. Stedman, David E. Thompson, Charles H. Treat, Martin H. Glynn, 1896, 1909-1911. undated (Box 86, Folder 364)
    - Central and South America: memoranda on investment potential in various countries, 1910, 1914, undated (Box 86, Folder 365)
    - Chesapeake Guaranty Company, 1910, undated (Box 86, Folder 366)
    - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions and speeches, 1903-1916 (Box 86, Folder 367-368)
    - Cuba, 1899, 1905-1906, 1911-1913, undated (Box 86, Folder 369)
    - Cuban Central Railways, Ltd., 1912-1913, undated (Box 86, Folder 370)
    - Dominican Republic: James M. Sullivan as ambassador, 1913, 1915, undated (Box 86, Folder 371)
    - Dominican Republic: memoranda concerning political and business conditions, 1912-1915, undated (Box 86, Folder 372)
    - Dominican Republic: National Bank of Santo Domingo and railroad construction, 1913, undated (Box 86, Folder 373)
    - Ecuador, 1899, 1911, undated (Box 86, Folder 374)
    - Fidelity and Casualty Co. of New York, The: account book, 1891 (Box 86, Folder 375)
    - insurance, 1910-1914 (Box 87, Folder 376)
    - International Fire Engine Co.International Harvester Company of America, 1909, undated 1906, 1911-1912, 1915 (Box 87, Folder 377)
    - Italian vote in the United States, 1912, undated (Box 87, Folder 378)
    - Italy: reports on agricultural development in southern Italy and Tripoli, probably prepared by WCB for the International Harvester Company, [1914?] (Box 87, Folder 379)
    - Lemon tariff: An act to reduce tariff duties and to provide revenue for the Government, and for other purposes, 1913 (Box 87, Folder 380)
    - Lemon tariff: California "lemon trust", 1904, 1911-1912, undated (Box 87, Folder 381)
    - Lemon tariff; Congressional bills and amendments, 1910-1914 (Box 87, Folder 382)
    - Lemon tariff; Congressional reports, 1910-1912 (Box 87, Folder 383)
    - Lemon tariff: memoranda by WCB and other miscellaneous material, 1911-1916 (Box 87, Folder 384)
    - Lemon tariff; newspaper clippings, 1910-1913, undated (Box 87, Folder 385-389)
    - Lemon tariff; petitions and circular letters, 1911, undated (Box 87, Folder 390)
    - Lemon tariff: printed material, 1907, 1910-1913 (Box 88, Folder 391)
    - Lemon tariff: scientific information concerning uses of citrus fruits, 1911-1912, undated (Box 88, Folder 392)
    - Lemon tariff: speeches, 1909, 1911-1912, undated (Box 88, Folder 393)
    - Lemon tariff: statistical information, 1903-1915 (Box 88, Folder 394)
    - Lemon tariff: testimony and briefs in hearings before the Committee on Ways and Means in favor of placing lemons on the free list, 1913 (Box 88, Folder 395)
    - Manila Navigation Company, 1900-1907 (Box 88, Folder 396)
    - memoranda of law and miscellaneous legal decisions, 1910-1915, undated (Box 88, Folder 397)
    - Mexico, 1908, 1913 (Box 88, Folder 398)
    - National City Bank, [1915?] (Box 88, Folder 399)
    - National Surety Company, 1892-1912, 1896 (Box 88, Folder 400-401)
    - navigation laws, undated (Box 88, Folder 402)
    - New York Life Insurance Company, 1900-1913 (Box 89, Folder 403)
    - New York Life Insurance Company: Grand Jury Minutes, 1906 December (Box 89, Folder 404)
    - New York Security and Trust Company investigation, 1907 (Box 89, Folder 405)
    - patents, 1912, undated (Box 89, Folder 406)
    - The People of the State of New York v. George W. Perkins, 1906-1907 (Box 89, Folder 407-408)
    - Perkins, George W. (Box 89, Folder 407-408)
    - Presidential campaign; autograph book, 1896 (Box 89, Folder 409)
    - Presidential campaign: Generals' Train, 1896 (Box 90, Folder 410)
    - Presidential campaign literature, 1896 (Box 90, Folder 411)
    - Presidential campaigns, 1900-1908 (Box 90, Folder 412)
    - prospectuses of various businesses and mining operations, 1900-1915 (Box 90, Folder 413)
    - prospectuses of various businesses and mining operations, 1900-1915 (Box 90, Folder 414)
    - Safety Car Heating and Lighting Company, 1913 (Box 90, Folder 415)
    - shipping: proposal for a steamship company to operate steamers between New York, Mediterranean ports and the East, [1914?] (Box 90, Folder 416)
    - speeches by; P. V. DeGraw, John A.Dix, Henry Sturges Drinker, Ralph M. Easley, Wade Ellis, Isaac Fuld, Martin H. Glynn, unidentified, 1912-1913, undated (Box 90, Folder 417)
    - Sugar tariff, 1908-1913 (Box 90, Folder 418)
    - tariffs (Box 90, Folder 419)
    - Theobald (William H.) v. William C. Beer, 1908-1909 (Box 90, Folder 420)
    - trusts (Box 90, Folder 421)
    - Underwood, Oscar W., 1905 (Box 90, Folder 422)
    - Washington Grocers' Exchange, 1913 (Box 90, Folder 423)
    - memoranda on unrelated topics, 1897-1915, undated (Box 90, Folder 424)
    - memoranda on financial matters, 1902-1915, undated (Box 90, Folder 425)
    - lists of persons and institutions, 1903-1911, undated (Box 90, Folder 426)
  - Personal Files
    - address book (Box 91, Folder 427)
    - bibliographies and miscellaneous verses by WCB and others, 1898 (Box 91, Folder 428)
    - business and calling cards (Box 91, Folder 429)
    - certificates of appointments and memberships, 1889, 1894, 1896 (Box 91, Folder 430)
    - diaries, 1868, 1873, 1884, 1901 (Box 91, Folder 431)
    - education: school notebooks and exercises, Circa 1873-1880 (Box 91, Folder 432)
    - education: United States Military Academy: invitations and programs, 1900, 1907, 1909 (Box 91, Folder 433)
    - education: United States Military Academy: memorabilia, 1880-1883, undated (Box 91, Folder 434)
    - education; United. States Military Academy; classbook, published in commemoration of the twenty-fifth anniversary of the graduation of the class of 1884, 1909 (Box 92, Folder 435)
    - education: United States Military Academy: Class of 1884 Bulletins, 1908-1915, 1917-1931, 1933-1939 (Box 92, Folder 436-438)
    - membership cards, passes and tickets, 1884-1916 (Box 92, Folder 439)